Gerry Mulligan Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-148, 160)
  - Just want to sing and dance like Fred Astaire
    - Lead sheet, For the Mel Tormé vocal compilation "Tentet with Tormé" (Box-folder 62/2)
  - K-4 Pacific
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Revised 2/86 (Box-folder 127/4)
    - Sketch score (Concert Jazz Band), Dated: 8/24/78 (Box-folder 39/1)
    - Score; parts (tentet), Dated: 1992 (Box-folder 138/8)
    - Score; part (baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 133/16)
    - Sketch scores (orchestra) (Box-folder 144/1)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts 1 (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 39/1)
    - Parts 2 (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 39/2)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Inscribed: CJB revised parts 6/88 (Box-folder 40/4)
    - Parts (Orchestra), On folder: Film masters (Box-folder 94/3)
    - Rhythm parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 89/2)
    - Parts (sextet), Baritone saxophone and guitar parts are missing (Box-folder 65/3)
    - Parts (orchestra - strings) (Box-folder 88/2, 89/1)
    - Parts (orchestra - woodwinds, perc., harp) (Box-folder 89/2)
    - Parts (tentet), From "Gig books" (Box-folder 113/3)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets; sketches; miscellaneous parts (Box-folder 8/13)
    - Sketches, Inscribed: For Brubeck (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Kaper
    - Lead sheets, From "Shorty Rogers" folder (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Keep talking
    - Sketches; lyric sheets, Laid in: letter from Paul Desmond regarding lyrics (Box-folder 18/15)
  - Killer Joe, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/2)
  - King of the road
    - Sketch scores (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Kinsey report, Judy Holliday; see also Holliday, Judy
    - Lyric sheets, Lyrics in the hand of Holliday (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Kitch, Gary McFarland
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 29/3)
  - Kitty city, Al Cohn
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 121/2)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 31/1)
  - La Paloma
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Claude Thornhill, the lost tunes, rec'd from Ken Poston 7/95 (Box-folder 47/3)
  - Lady be good, George Gershwin
    - Score; sketches; parts, For the "Tormé / Kool tour" (Box-folder 119/2)
    - Score (8 measures); parts, On folder: Rebirth of the Cool (Box-folder 62/9)
    - Part (bass), Last 8 measures only; From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Lady Chatterley's mother
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 26/2)
  - Lady Coryell, Larry Coryell
    - Lead sheets; sketches (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Lady is a tramp
    - Part (unidentified), From "Standards" folder (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Sketch, From "Misc. sextet parts" folder (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Larko, Gale Madden
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/17)
  - Lazy, Irving Berlin
    - Score (big band), For the recording Holliday with Mulligan (Box-folder 117/2)
    - Parts (big band), For the recording Holliday with Mulligan (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Leave it to me
    - Lead sheets, On folder: New quartet, 6/24/94 (Box-folder 23A/1)
    - Lead sheets, On folder: LA tunes LV 2 me 1 and 2 (Box-folder 22/13)
  - Leeway, Lee Konitz
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/6)
  - Lestorian mode, John Carisi
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 50/8)
  - Let it snow
    - Score; oversize (big band), Ralph Burns arrangement for Judy Holliday album (Box-folder 148/2)
    - Parts (big band), Ralph Burns arrangement for Judy Holliday album (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Let sleeping tigers
    - Score, Incomplete? (Box-folder 20/3)
  - The light in the icebox
    - Parts, From Quinnipiac concert; On verso: Vibes part for Valentine, 3/25/68 (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Like someone in love
    - Part (baritone saxophone), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Lillibet
    - Sketch, On folder: Original sketch from 1952 (Box-folder 24/5)
  - Limelight
    - Score (big band), GM arrangement for Stan Kenton Orchestra (Box-folder 133/11)
    - Parts (big band), GM arrangement for Stan Kenton Orchestra (Box-folder 54/3)
    - Parts (big band), GM arrangement for Stan Kenton Orchestra (Box-folder 51/4)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Line for Lyons
    - Score; parts; lead sheets, Arrangement for Itzhak Perlman (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Score; parts; lead sheets, Arrangement for Vinnie Burke (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Phil Sunkel arrangement (Box-folder 118/8)
    - Score; parts (orchestra), On folder: Rochester Phil., 5/19-20/1989, arr. John Dankworth; Laid in: program and notes (Box-folder 144/4)
    - Score; sketches; part (flugel horn) (tentet) (Box-folder 138/6)
    - Parts (orchestra: strings), On folder: Rochester Phil., 5/19-20/1989 (Box-folder 108/2)
    - Parts (tentet), From "Gig books" (Box-folder 113/2)
    - Parts, On folder: Small band trumpet parts (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets; sketches, From "Misc. sextet parts" folder (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Sketches (Box-folder 67/8)
  - Listening to Astor
    - Score; parts, For the 1995 recording Dragonfly (Box-folder 68/6)
    - Sketch scores, For the 1995 recording Dragonfly (Box-folder 140/13)
    - Sketch score (Box-folder 140/10)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Little Big Horn
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Rhythm section parts are missing (Box-folder 125/3)
    - Score; parts; sketches; cue sheets, Dave Grusin arrangement for recording session, May 1981 (Box-folder 136/5)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts; sketches (album rejects) (Box-folder 57/3)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Little girl blue, Rodgers and Hart
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Manny Album arrangement (Box-folder 122/8)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Manny Album arrangement (Box-folder 31/2)
  - Little girls, Terry Gibbs
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/3)
  - Little glory road
    - Score; parts, Slide Hampton arrangement for the 1995 recording Dragonfly (Box-folder 140/8)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets; song lists (quartet), On folder: New songs for quartet 2-9-93, originals (Box-folder 23/12)
  - Little Rock getaway
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Al Cohn arrangement (Box-folder 120/5)
    - Part (guitar), GM personal performance part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Al Cohn arrangement (Box-folder 30/3)
  - Little Willie
    - Lead sheets, From "Kai Winding" folder (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Lollipop
    - Parts (sextet, 4 horn score) (Box-folder 140/2)
    - Part (tenor saxophone) (Box-folder 58/6)
    - Lead sheets; sketches, From "Misc. sextet parts" folder (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Londonderry Air
    - Parts (sextet) (Box-folder 52/8)
  - Lonesome Boulevard
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets, On folder: Includes Carriage House date 3/14/89 (Box-folder 20/15)
  - A long song
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 43/1)
  - A long, long key
    - Lead sheets; song lists (quartet), On folder: New songs for quartet 2-9-93, originals (Box-folder 23/12)
  - Looking for you
    - Parts (quintet), For quintet recording with Gerry Niewood (Box-folder 65/4)
  - Lord built the house
    - Part (baritone saxophone), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Lost and found
    - Lead sheet, On folder: New songs for quartet 2/9/93, originals (Box-folder 23/12)
  - Lost in his arms / Best thing for you
    - Score, On folder: Maragret Whiting, arrangements; Hubert Arnold arrangement (Box-folder 137/5)
  - Lost in the stars, Kurt Weill
    - Sketches; part (bass) (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Louisiana
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Love is the sweetest thing
    - Score (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Score (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 117/5)
    - Parts (piano, guitar only) (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Parts (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 4/13)
  - Love jumped out, Buck Clayton
    - Parts, Incomplete; Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Love letters, Victor Young
    - Lead sheets; sketches, On folder: Arr. ideas for Q (Box-folder 64/4)
  - Love of my life, Roger Kellaway
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/16)
  - Love song to a tree
    - Part (baritone saxophone); lead sheet (Box-folder 64/4)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: New songs for quartet 2/9/93, originals (Box-folder 23/12)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 22/22)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 24/2)
  - Love walked in
    - Piano part (chords) (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Lead sheet (chord changes), From "Standards" folder (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Lovelight, Laura Taylor
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/19)
  - Lover man
    - Parts (Concert Jazz band), On folder: Claude Thornhill, the lost tunes, rec'd from Ken Poston 7/95 (Box-folder 47/2)
  - Loving you
    - Score (big band), For the recording Holliday with Mulligan (Box-folder 147/4)
    - Parts (big band), For the recording Holliday with Mulligan (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Lead sheets with lyrics, For the recording Holliday with Mulligan (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Lead sheet, For the Mel Tormé vocal compilation "Tentet with Tormé" (Box-folder 62/6)
  - Lu and Shu, Lee Konitz
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/6)
  - Lucky day
    - Parts (big band), On folder: Gil Evans arrangement for Benny Goodman (Box-folder 61/3)
  - Lullaby of Mexico
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Lunasea, Peggy Stern
    - Lead sheet; parts (Box-folder 23A/5)
  - Lush Life
    - Parts (sextet) (Box-folder 65/2)
    - Score (sextet) (Box-folder 140/4)
    - Lead sheets; sketches (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Luv [film, 1967]
    - Scores; cue sheets; lyrics (Box-folder 117/6)
    - Lead sheets; notes (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Lyric ideas by GM
    - Lyric sheets; sketches (Box-folder 21/11)
  - Magpie
    - Lead sheet; parts (bass, piano) (Box-folder 19/2)
  - Mahler Sunday
    - Sketches (Box-folder 21/7)
  - Mainstream
    - Sketch score; parts, Incomplete; From "Misc. sextet parts" folder (Box-folder 66/8)
    - Lead sheets; sketches, From "Misc. sextet parts" folder (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Major and the minor
    - Score, GM arrangement for Claude Thornhill, 1947 November 24 (Box-folder 146/5)
  - Makin' whoopee
    - Parts (bass, drums), From "Standards" folder (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Mama Flosie, Al Cohn
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 121/3)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 29/2)
  - Man on the run blues
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Manior de mes reves, Django Reinhardt
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 26/1)
  - March and April blues
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Incomplete (Box-folder 127/5)
    - Sketches (Box-folder 59/2)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 127/5)
  - Margarita see also Marguerite
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets; notes, From "Brasilian collection" folder (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Margerine, Hal Galper
    - Lead sheet, On verso: bass part for "Freeway" (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Marguerite see also Margarita
    - Lead sheets, Laid in: note from Gordon Jack to GM, 1988 October 5 (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Marion Ohio mon amour
    - Lead sheets, On folder: Make new copy for Mel Tormé (Box-folder 20/4)
  - May be wrong, Shorty Rogers
    - Parts (1st alto saxophone), From "Shorty Rogers" folder (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Maytag
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 126/1)
    - Score, For the recording The age of steam (Box-folder 134/2)
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), On title page: Version Z, revised 2/26/86 (Box-folder 126/2)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 37/3)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On title page: Version Z, revised 2/26/86 (Box-folder 126/2)
    - Parts, Trombone 2 and 3 and drums parts are missing; For the recording The age of steam (Box-folder 134/2)
    - Parts (big band), On folder: Parts for "Jazz Gala Peter Herbolzheimer Band," Jan. 1976, West Germany (Box-folder 49/2)
    - Parts (trumpet), On folder: Quartet trumpet parts - originals (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets; rhythm section parts (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Sketches for piano and bass parts, On folder: Quartet trumpet parts - originals (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Melba's blues, Melba Liston; Other title: Now ain't it!
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 19/10)
  - Memories of you, Eubie Blake
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
  - La menace [film, 1977]
    - Lead sheets for "Theme from La menace" (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Lead sheets; notes; film cues (Box-folder 53/7)
    - Lead sheets (cue 2, cue 19) (Box-folder 53/8)
    - Lead sheets (cue rejects) (Box-folder 53/8)
    - Lead sheets for recording (Box-folder 54/2)
    - Lead sheets, Tom Fay arrangement (Box-folder 53/8)
    - Lead sheet; part (baritone/alto saxophone), Tom Fay arrangement (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 24/3)
  - Mercedes bend, John Eardley
    - Sketch scores, On folder: For bari and trumpet (Box-folder 145/16)
  - Mexico Otra Vez
    - Sketch score (Box-folder 137/4)
  - Mezzanine
    - Lead sheets, Yale Jazz Festival, 1988; On folder: GM parts, Kelly and Mike's tunes (Box-folder 67/7)
  - Mi sono innamorato di te, Luigi Tenco
    - Lead sheet, From Milan, Tebetan Gala, 1995 October (Box-folder 19/7)
  - Midas lives
    - Score (tentet) (Box-folder 138/1)
    - Parts (tentet), From "Gig books" (Box-folder 113/7)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: New quartet, 6/24/1994 (Box-folder 23A/1)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: 12/3/1991 (Box-folder 62/5)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 23A/1)
  - Milano
    - Sketches; notes on lyrics (Box-folder 21/9)
    - Parts (extra baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 80/2)
  - Milesign, Gary McFarland
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Gary McFarland arrangement (Box-folder 121/6)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Gary McFarland arrangement (Box-folder 31/6)
  - Minor blues
    - Lead sheet, On folder: GM parts, Kelly and Mike's tunes (Box-folder 67/7)
  - Minor vamp, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Miss me, a little
    - Lead sheets with lyrics, Lyrics by Marty Brill (Box-folder 18/16)
  - Monkian 'round, Lee Konitz
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/6)
  - Moon dreams
    - Parts (nonet), Gil Evans arrangement; Parts transcribed by Gunther Schuller (Box-folder 61/5)
    - Parts (tentet), From "Gig books" (Box-folder 112/2)
  - Moon mist, Duke Ellington
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Moonlight in Vermont, John Blackburn / Karl Suessdorf
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 121/5)
    - Score, Hubert Arnold arrangement; On folder: Margaret Whiting, arrangements (Box-folder 137/5)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 31/5)
    - Parts (trumpet, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone), From "Standards" folder (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Morning star
    - Folder (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Charts not in book (Box-folder 49/4)
  - Motel
    - Score (big band), GM arrangement for Ray Anthony Orchestra (Box-folder 133/2)
    - Parts (big band), GM arrangement for Ray Anthony Orchestra (Box-folder 55/3)
  - Move, Denzil Best
    - Score (nonet), John Lewis arrangement (Box-folder 137/6)
    - Parts (tentet), From "Gig books" (Box-folder 112/3)
  - Mr. President, Irving Berlin
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Incomplete (Box-folder 118/4)
  - Mrs. Warren's progression
    - Sketches, From "Misc. works, some for Count Basie Band" folder (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Mud bug
    - Score (sextet), On folder: Sextet - 4 horn scores by Jerry Hurwitz (Lloyd) (Box-folder 140/2)
  - Mullenium
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: C.B.S. date 1957 (Box-folder 132/9)
    - Sketch score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Apr. 1951 (Box-folder 132/10)
  - Mulligan with organs, John Guarnieri
    - Sketch (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Music for a Monday afternoon
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Manny Albam arrangement (Box-folder 122/9)
  - Music for baritone saxophone and orchestra
    - Parts: Part 1 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Parts: Part 2 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Parts; conductor's score: Part 3 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Parts: Part 4 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - My friend
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/1)
  - My friend Buddy, Terry Gibbs
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/3)
  - My funny Valentine, Richard Rodgers and Lorenz Hart
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 122/6)
    - Sketch scores; parts (2 sets) (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 33/2)
    - Parts (bass), From "Synclavier" folders (Box-folder 20/10)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Parts (bass, trombone-sketch), From "Standards" folder (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Sketches for trumpet, piano, and bass parts (Box-folder 12/7)
  - My kind of love
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 121/7)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 32/4)
  - My man's gone now
    - Sketches (Box-folder 59/3)
    - Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 59/3)
    - Parts (rhythm section) (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - My romance, Rodgers and Hammerstein
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - My shining hour, Harold Arlen / Johnny Mercer
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - My ship
    - Sketches of score, On folder: New ideas for recording date, 4/95 (Box-folder 64/2)
    - Part (bass), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Nearness
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 43/3)
  - Neo darlin', Other title: Sweet William
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 118/7)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Never again
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Never git lonely, Gale Madden
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 18/17)
  - New era
    - Parts, On folder: For John Graas (Box-folder 56/10)
  - New light, Ted Rosenthal
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 8/1)
  - New Orleans, Hoagy Carmichael
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 53/6)
  - New piano blues
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 42/1)
  - New shoes
    - Sketches; notes on lyrics (Box-folder 21/9)
  - New wine, From the 1977 film La menace
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 10/6)
  - News from Blueport, Bill Crow
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/9)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: Art Farmer, Lincoln Center '94, The art of trumpet (Box-folder 24/1)
  - Nick's tune
    - Lead sheet, From "Kai Winding" folder (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Night and day
    - Score (big band), GM arrangement for the Stan Kenton Orchestra (Box-folder 133/3)
    - Score (big band), Dated: 2/52; On folder: Arr. for Stan Kenton Orch. (Box-folder 133/4)
  - Night lights
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: 1 chorus, out chorus (Box-folder 124/2)
    - Score (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 117/5)
    - Parts (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Parts (bass, guitar, trumpet, piano) (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Incomplete; On folder: 1 chorus, out chorus (Box-folder 31/3)
    - Parts (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets; piano part (Box-folder 10/3)
    - Lead sheet, For the Mel Tormé vocal compilation "Tentet with Tormé" (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Lead sheets; lyric sheets (Box-folder 12/1)
  - The night of the roadrunner
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Holman arrangement (Box-folder 123/3)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Holman arrangement (Box-folder 42/4)
  - Night ride
    - Score; parts, John Murtaugh arrangement (Box-folder 44/1)
  - Night song, Barry Manilow
    - Lead sheet; parts (piano, baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Nights at the turntable
    - Parts (quintet), Published "Mulliganettes" series (Box-folder 10/7)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 10/9)
    - Lead sheet, From "Misc. sextet parts" folder (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Nine lives
    - Score; parts (tentet), On title page: Revised 5/1/1992 (Box-folder 130/2)
    - Scores (tentet), One score is incomplete (Box-folder 130/1)
    - Miscellaneous tentet song list, On folder: 12/3/1991 (Box-folder 62/5)
    - Parts (tentet), From "Gig books" (Box-folder 113/6)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone, piano) (Box-folder 23/2)
  - Ninth life
    - Parts (small band), For the 1995 recording Dragonfly (Box-folder 68/8)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - No. 1 see also Aire de Buenos Aires
    - Parts (baritone saxophone, guitar) (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/4)
  - No. 2
    - Parts (baritone saxophone, bass, drums, piano, vibes, guitar) (Box-folder 12/3)
    - Lead sheets (sextet), Two versions (Box-folder 12/3)
  - No. 3
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Lead sheets, From "Brasilian collection" folder (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Noblese
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)